ningtube.com 2012-03-14

# NingTube | Privacy Policy

**** **

###### PERSONAL INFORMATION

###### We at NingTube respect the privacy concerns of the users of this site and have created this privacy policy to explain, Browsing NingTube You can Watch Videos,Images and Listen Audios  on NingTube without having a NingTube Account. You also can contact us through the NingTube Help Center or by emailing us directly without having to register for an account.  
Your NingTube Account. For some activities on NingTube, like uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos, or watching restricted videos, you need a NingTube. We ask for some personal information when you create an account,including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. Usage Information. When you use NingTube, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels, groups and favorites you subscribe to, which other users you communicate with, the videos you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in NingTube (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your NingTube Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a tag (also called a "web beacon") in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery.Content Uploaded to Site. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others. If you download the NingTube Uploader, your copy includes a unique application number. This number, and information about your installation of the Uploader (version number, language) will be sent to NingTube when the Uploader automatically checks for updates and will be used to update your version of the Uploader. 

###### USERS

###### If you submit personal information to NingTube, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of NingTube, and to process any flagging activity or other communication you send to us.  
We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. We may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when: a). We have your consent to share the information b). We have to cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities c). we respond to subpoenas, court orders in compliance with the legal process. d). when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property.When you create a NingTube Account, some information about your NingTube Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of NingTube. This may include the date you opened your NingTube Account, the date you last logged into your NingTube Account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of videos you have watched.Your NingTube Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on NingTube, such as when you upload videos or send messages through NingTube. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.Any videos that you submit to NingTube may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other NingTube users or the general public.  
You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your NingTube Account channel page. If you choose to add certain features to your NingTube Account channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your friends or other users. Such shared activity may include your favorite videos, videos you rated and videos that you have uploaded. 

###### YOUR CHOICES

###### If you have a NingTube Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, email preferences and privacy settings at any time by visiting your account profile page.  
You may control the information that is available to other users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your NingTube Account and the features that are included on your channel page. If you have enabled Active Sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your account name, not your email address, are watching the same video.  
You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through NingTube, in which case you can still view videos and explore NingTube, but NingTube may not be able to provide certain services to you. We are not partner or link with any video sharing network still we thankful Youtube, Daily Motion and Google who allow our site to use their videos on our network.When we use anyvideo of Youtube,Dailymotion and google we don't remove their brand,tag or logo.

###### THIRD PARTY AND SPONSOR ADS

###### we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Ads that appear on NingTube and occasionally at all pages are sponsor ads by  Google AdSense. we do not personally endorse the products and services advertised in these ads.

###### USE OF COOKIES:

###### NingTube does use cookies on its Web site, mostly in order to track traffic coming from other Web sites and leaving to other Web sites. We do not use the cookies to attempt to link them with individuals to make any information personally identifiable. we track our visitors with our different technology

###### 3rd PARTIES COOKIES

###### Various advertisers or affiliate merchants on this site may use cookies. Typically it is click stream data so that merchants may ascertain statistical and referral information. However, we do not know specifically what, if any information they may collect.This is beyond our control and we do not accept any liability regarding 3rd party cookies. We therefore refer to respective privacy policies.  

###### UPDATE AND CHANGES IN THE PRIVACY POLICY

###### We reserve the rights to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes which we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We suggest that you regularly check NingTube Policy for updates.

**
